hai91.com 2008-12-25

# Privacy And Anti Spam Policy - Free SMS @ Hai91

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
 **Privacy And Anti Spam Policy**

At HAI91, we respect and take steps to protect the privacy of our Users. We strive to make our site a safe environment for all who use HAI91 services. We are committed to providing you the best possible online experience as well as the best products and services. This policy addresses our practices with respect to our website, but does not address the practices of any website we link to (including the merchants and content providers we link to). This policy is incorporated into, and subject to the terms of, our Terms and Conditions.

We use the information you provide us (during registration process etc) to keep track of the HAI91 products and services that you have signed up to receive. Though the senders name shall be displayed as HAI91.com ( or HAI91â€™s mobile number in case of CDMA subscriber) your mobile number, as recorded in your profile, shall be appended at the end of your personal message. This way the recipient knows who the sender of the SMS is. We will use contextual advertising in user generated SMS.Deliverimg Contextual advertisement and related links is the key to provide the users the FREE service. HAI91stores and processes your SMS messages. This is completely automated process with no human intervention.

We may also use your personal information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze our website usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our website's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our website and better tailor it to meet our Users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We will use your email address to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news from time to time. We will use information in the file we maintain about you, and any other information that we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, in order to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems and to enforce our Terms and Conditions.

Any information/content that is sent to HAI91 for SMS text messaging and/or storage purposes will remain the property of the User. HAI91 will at no time collect or redistribute this information without obtaining your consent, except where legally required by law to do so. This has particular reference to any database, numbers and/or recipient details that you may deliver to us, or store on our databases.

As a matter of policy, we neither rent nor sell personally identifiable information about our Users to any third party. We may however aggregate all personally identifiable information and may disclose such aggregated information to any or all advertisers, marketing and general or commercial promotional purposes. Even in these cases, disclosure of any information that could personally identify you would not be permitted.

HAI91 may offer some features where sometimes it is required to provide some of the information about you to a third party, which is offering such services. It must be understood clearly that we will provide information only to the extent that the said third party requires your information, which enables you to use their service, but prior to that we will make efforts to notify you of specific information being provided to such third parties. Before you use the services of any third party, we request you to check up and evaluate if the terms and conditions of said third party services are acceptable to you.

It is vital that HAI91 receives from you the permission and valid rights to transmit your information to a third party. In addition, please note that we will comply completely and fully with any or all court orders, information requests or otherwise from government agencies and regulators and any other legal and regulatory processes that require us to disclose personally identifiable information of our Users.

It is also vital that HAI91 receives from you the permission and Valid rights to, and that you have no objection to append targeted Ads to your FREE SMS messages. By using our FREE SMS messaging services you are actually confirming that you have gone through our terms and conditions and that you have no objection to in our appending targeted Ads to your SMS messages and to using your personal information.  
ANTI SPAM POLICY

Any registered User of HAI91 can send SMS text messages to his/her friends, family, colleagues, clients, contacts etc using the HAI91 Interface. These interface conditions of use strictly forbid spamming to cell phone Users. We have several software filters to block spam messages. However, we cannot guarantee that spamming will not ever occur. Please let us know (email to support@hai91.com) the details of the message like content of message, time of delivery, sender name or number etc so that we can immediately check and block the user responsible for the same.

Appending contextual Ads to users SMS is not considered as spam within the meaning of spam. Spam is a totally uninvited message urging the recipient to avail of some services. But here the advertisement is part of a personal message which the recipient receives and is not a totally uninvited message. Also, the user has specifically opted-in to use this FREE service to send SMS to the recipient. Further the communication is between two known persons.   
LIMITS ON OUR ABILITIES

Although your privacy is our top priority, due to the existing statutory, legal and technical environment, we are unable to ensure that personally identifiable information of our Users will not be disclosed to third parties in ways that are not described in this policy. Additionally, we may (and here you give us authorization to) disclose any private information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials, which we may believe to be necessary at our sole discretion or appropriate to address or to resolve inquiries or problems. We undertake that this will not be done for commercial purposes or for our personal gain.

If you have any further questions about our privacy and anti-spam policy or about its implementation, please email us at support@hai91.com

You hereby acknowledge that the acceptance of this privacy policy is a condition to your use of our products and services and that you agree to be bound by all of our Terms and Conditions.
